 export const data = [
            {
            question: "Which African country is known for its vibrant fashion industry, particularly in cities like Lagos?",
              option1: "Kenya",
              option2: "Nigeria",
              option3: "South Africa",
              option4: "Ghana",
              ans: 2,
            },
          {
            question: "Which traditional fabric is commonly worn in West Africa and is often handmade?",
              option1: "Kente",
              option2: "Ankara",
              option3: "Dashiki",
              option4: "Shweshwe",
              ans: 2,
          },
          {
            question: "Which African city is considered a hub for luxury fashion brands in the continent?",
              option1: "Johannesburg",
              option2: "Accra",
              option3: "Cairo",
              option4: "Nairobi",
              ans: 1,
        },
          {
            question: "What is the name of the fabric often used in traditional Nigerian fashion that has become a global trend?",
              option1: "Kente",
              option2: "Adire",
              option3: "Shweshwe",
              option4: "Khanga",
              ans: 2,
        },
          {
            question: "Which African fashion designer is known for showcasing African prints in international fashion weeks?",
              option1: "Laduma Ngxokolo",
              option2: "Tiffany Amber",
              option3: "Deola Sagoe",
              option4: "Ozwald Boateng",
              ans: 3,
        },
          {
            question: "What is the name of the African fashion event that has gained global recognition?",
              option1: "Africa Fashion Week",
              option2: "Lagos Fashion and Design Week",
              option3: "Cape Town Fashion Week",
              option4: "Arise Fashion Week",
              ans: 2,
        },
          {
            question: "Which country is famous for producing high-quality cotton that is exported worldwide?",
              option1: "Ethiopia",
              option2: "Nigeria",
              option3: "Egypt",
              option4: "Ivory Coast",
              ans: 3
        },
          {
            question: "Which African fabric is known for its bold patterns and vibrant colors, commonly used in both formal and casual attire?",
              option1: "Ankara",
              option2: "Kente",
              option3: "Bogolan",
              option4: "Dashiki",
              ans: 1,
        },
          {
            question: "Which financial practice is common among African fashion entrepreneurs to fund their businesses?",
              option1: "Crowdfunding",
              option2: "Microfinancing",
              option3: "Venture Capital",
              option4: "Bank Loans",
              ans: 2,
        },
          {
            question: "Which of these African fashion markets is known for its luxury clientele and high fashion exports?",
              option1: "South Africa",
              option2: "Nigeria",
              option3: "Morocco",
              option4: "Kenya",
              ans: 1,
        },
          {
            question: "Which economic factor is often a challenge for African fashion designers when pricing their goods locally?",
              option1: "Currency devaluation",
              option2: "High import tariffs",
              option3: "Low consumer income",
              option4: "Taxation",
              ans: 3,
        },
          {
            question: "What is the name of the fashion capital of Morocco known for its leather goods and textiles?",
              option1: "Casablanca",
              option2: "Marrakech",
              option3: "Tangier",
              option4: "Rabat",
              ans: 2,
        },
          {
            question: "Which East African country is gaining recognition for its ethical fashion practices and sustainable designs?",
              option1: "Tanzania",
              option2: "Uganda",
              option3: "Rwanda",
              option4: "Kenya",
              ans: 4,
        },
          {
            question: "Which African luxury fashion house is known for its bespoke suits and has dressed celebrities globally?",
              option1: "Ozwald Boateng",
              option2: "David Tlale",
              option3: "Maxhosa",
              option4: "Mai Atafo",
              ans: 1,
        },
          {
            question: "Which financial concept allows African fashion entrepreneurs to pay for goods and services later while selling their products immediately?",
              option1: "Layaway",
              option2: "Microloan",
              option3: "Buy Now, Pay Later",
              option4: "Credit Line",
              ans: 3,
        },
        ];


//  {
//     question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection",
//     // options: ["Computer", "Mobile", "Tablet", "Laptop"],
//     // answer: 0,
//     option1: "Computer",
//     option2: "Mobile",
//     option3: "Tablet",
//     option4: "Laptop",
//     ans: 1,